S01E20 挽救房子
S01E20  Be a man
杰森:我还是认为在我们去看你的父母之前应该先打个电话给他们.
Jason: I still think we should call first before we go all the way on the bus to see your folks.
麦琪:杰森,他们就会说让我们不要去.
Maggie: Jason, they'd just tell us not to come.
迈克:哦,来吧,我来帮你弄那些东西吧,爸爸.
Mike: Oh, here, let me get all those for you, dad.
麦琪:开萝尔宝贝,我们差不多好了.
Maggie: Carol honey, we are almost ready.
开萝尔:你是在和我说话吗?可谁也没跟我说制定了这个旅行计划.
Carol: Were you speaking to me? No one spoke to me when this trip was being planned.
麦琪:宝贝,直到昨天晚上我们还不知道我们是否要去.开萝尔,我们担心你的外公外婆.
Maggie: Honey, we didn't know we were going until last night. Carol, we are worried about grandpa and grandma.
杰森:噢,麦琪,我想你太过担心了.
Jason: oh, Maggie, I think you are overreacting.
麦琪:为什么他们直到最后一刻才取消到这儿的旅行?为什么爸爸说一切都很顺利呢?
Maggie: Then why did they call to cancel the trip at the last minute? And why did my dad say everything was swell?
杰森:啊……那是因为确实一切都很顺利.
Jason: Ah&amp;amp;because it is.
麦琪:不,杰森,我父亲不用类似"顺利","好","不错"这样的词.
Maggie: No, Jason, my father doesn't use words like 'swell', 'good' or 'nice'...
杰森:当然不会说了,如果我也闷在家里的话.
Jason: Certainly not when I'm in the room.
本:我们走,我们走,我们走!
Ben: Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
麦琪:你怎么这么兴奋,本?
Maggie: Well you sure are excited about this, Ben?
本:你开玩笑吧?外公会让我玩他的荧光棒,他的手铐,甚至还会让我戴他的徽章.
Ben: Are you kidding? Grandpa is going to let me use his night stick, and his handcuffs, and even wear his badge.
杰森:嘿,可能还让你留指纹呢.
Jason: Hey, maybe you'll get finger printed, too.
本:噢!
Ben: Wow!
迈克:噢,爸爸,再次谢谢你让我留在家里帮塞克斯先生的草地施肥挣点钱.当然我认为挣钱能帮助我尊敬金钱,帮助我长大成人.
Mike: Well, Dad, again I just want to thank you for letting me stay home and earn some extra money helping Mr. Sacks fertilize his lawn. I am sure that earning money will teach me a new respect for the dollar, and help me grow as a person.
杰森:你肯定会精通如何施肥的.
Jason: But you'll be pretty good at spreading manure too.
迈克:很遗憾,说实在的,我错过了围在外婆的钢琴边听她唱歌的机会.
Mike: I'm so sorry that I'm gonna miss that sing along around grandma's piano.
杰森:对!记住孩子,如果你有什么问题就给隔壁的库斯曼家打电话.只能留一个客人过夜.
Jason: Well, just remember if you have any problems you can call the Crusons next door. And only one guest stays over tonight.
开萝尔:这不公平.没人关心我开萝尔有没有别的计划.在这个家里没人把我当作真正的活人看待.
Carol: This is not fair. No one thought that old Carol might have other plans.  No one in this entire house treated me as a real living breathing human person.
麦琪:开萝尔,上车.再见,宝贝.哦,还有迈克,我知道一切都会顺利,
Maggie: Carol, get in the car. Bye, sweetheart. Oh and Mike, I know everything will be fine,
因为如果有什么事……我们会一直关你到35岁.
because if it is...you'll be grounded until you are 35.
迈克:都说了几遍了.再见妈妈,再见爸爸.
Mike: Enough said.  Bye mom, bye dad.
杰森:明天见,迈克.
Jason: See you tomorrow Mike.
迈克:好,再见……耶!
Mike: Alright, bye-bye ....Yeah!
麦琪:本,等等我们.
Maggie: Ben, wait for us.
本:我要去洗手间.
Ben: I got to go to the bathroom.
麦琪:我们想一起给外公外婆一个惊喜.
Maggie: We want to surprise grandpa and grandma together.
本:如果外公在我走之前搜我的身,我一定能让他惊喜.
Ben: If grandpa starts frisking to me before I go, I will surprise him all right.
麦琪:嘿.
Maggie: Hi.
一对夫妇:嘿.
A couple: Hi.
麦琪:我是埃德和凯特的女儿麦琪.
Maggie: I'm Ed and Kate's daughter, Maggie.
男人:哦好.对不起……
Man: Oh good. Excuse us..
麦琪:啊……你们就这样子走进去吗?
Maggie: Ah... should you just walk in like that?
男人:哦,难道让我们敲门,然后在冷风里等某个混蛋来开门?
Man: Well, we should knock, stand out here in the cold, waiting for some jerk to open the door?
麦琪:别这样.
Maggie: Come on.
杰森:他们是谁?
Jason: Who are they?
开萝尔:妈妈,这些人就是你不给他们送圣诞卡片的亲戚吗?我去找外公外婆了.
Carol: Mom, are these people the relatives you don't send Christmas cards to? I'm gonna try to find grandma and grandpa.
生意人:哈,乡亲们进来吧.哦你们把行李也拿来了.别担心,我们在晚饭前能谈好生意的.孩子们也来了.那太好了.来杯鸡尾酒弗兰克?
Salesman: ha, hiya folks come in. Oh I see you brought your luggage. Well don't worry, we'll try and close this deal by nightfall. The kiddies too. This is so nice. Cocktail Frank?
本:我不叫弗兰克.
Ben: My name is not Frank.
麦琪:你是谁?
Maggie: Who are you?
男人:我是谁?
Man: Who am I?
麦琪:我不认识你,也不认识他.
Maggie: I don't know you, I don't know him.
生意人:哈里·皮特,美国梦化为现实公司.
Salesman: Harry Dimbo, Great American-dream realty company
麦琪:这个房子要卖掉吗?
Maggie: This house is for sale?
生意人:是的.
Salesman: Yes.
麦琪:但……房主在哪?
Maggie: But.. where are the owners?
生意人:哦,卖主是不会露面的.特别是花了三十年造房子的房主.这会让他们心碎的.
Salesman: Oh, the sellers are never present for the showing. Especially sellers who have put thirty years into a place. This would break their heart.
麦琪:是的.
Maggie: I'm sure.
杰森:哦,亲爱的,这房子还没卖掉呢.
Jason: Well, honey they haven't sold it yet.
生意人:你们对这个房子感兴趣吗?
Salesman: You folks are interested in this house?
麦琪:很感兴趣.
Maggie: Deeply.
生意人:哦,让我来指出这个不朽杰作的几个突出优点.
Salesman: Oh, Let me point out some fine features of this timeless classic.
麦琪:你那样做的话我会哭的.
Maggie: If you do. I'm going to cry.
生意人:你说什么?
Salesman: Pardon?
杰森:嗯,他们为什么要卖这房子?
Jason: en. Why are they selling?
生意人:你们对这房子的特点不感兴趣吗?
Salesman: you are not interested in hearing about the house?
麦琪:我爱这房子,我就在这个火炉边做功课,等我爸爸回家把他的枪挂好然后过来抱我.
Maggie: I love this house, I do my homework right by this fireplace waiting for my daddy to come home and hang up his gun and give a hug.
杰森:他们为什么要卖这房子?
Jason: Why are they selling?
生意人:哦,别人的秘密我不能随便说,但我简单地告诉你们,靠退休收入,又贷了款,还遭了难而且……
Salesman: Oh, well, I can't really violate their confidence, but I will say, retirement income, a loan payment, disaster&amp;amp;
麦琪:哦.
Maggie: Oh.
杰森:没事,我是她的心理医生.
Jason: Its alright, I'm her psychiatrist.
生意人:哦,有什么我帮得上的吗?
Salesman: Oh, well, can I do anything?
杰森:是的,你就让我们单独呆一会,谢谢你.
Jason: Yes, you can just give us a moment alone please, thank you.
杰森:好了,麦琪,亲爱的.行了,我们想想看这件事.
Jason: Come on, Maggie, sweetheart. Come on, we'll look into this.
麦琪:卖掉这房子会上伤了他们的心.
Maggie: Selling this house has to be breaking their hearts.
杰森:我知道.为什么他们不来找我们呢?
Jason: I know. Why didn't they come to us for help?
麦琪:哦,我爸爸的自尊心很强,他怎么会开口向我们要钱呢?他对你谋生的工作有想法.
Maggie: Oh, my father's pride. There's no way he could ask us for money knowing the way he feels about what you do for a living.
杰森:你说什么?
Jason: What?
麦琪:没什么,我随便说的.
Maggie: Forget, I said that.
杰森:我知道他不太喜欢我,但我没想到他还讨厌我的工作.
Jason: I knew he didn't care for me, I didn't think he even hated my entire profession.
麦琪:哦,亲爱的,他并不是讨厌你的工作,他只是不了解你的工作是什么.
Maggie: Oh, honey, it's not that he hates your profession, it's just that he doesn't know what it is.
杰森:哦,那么17年后我才知道这些……
Jason: Oh, so now after 17 years I find this out...
麦琪:我告诉你他认为你是个江湖医生有什么好处呢?
Maggie: Now what good would it have done to let you know he thinks you are a quack?
杰森:江湖医生?
Jason: A quack?
麦琪:杰森,我们以后再谈这个好吗?现在我想在和爸爸妈妈见面以前不能让这房子卖掉.
Maggie: Jason, can we talk about this later? Now I don't want this house sold until we get a chance to talk to mom and dad.
杰森:对,对.
Jason: Sure, sure.
生意人:真正的双层板条,密封牢固,真正的窄立柱.
Salesman: Genuine lacken plaster, on real two by four studs.
杰森:对不起,我不是有意打断你,哈里,你刚才说的我没怎么听清楚.那么是在这间房间还是在整个房子里发现碎尸的呢?
Jason: Excuse me, I don't mean to interrupt you, Harry. What you were saying over there confused me. Were the victim's bodies found in this room or all through the house?
门铃响了.
The door bell rang.
鲍纳:生活就应该这样.
Boner: This is life as it should be.
贝迪:迈克,迈克!
Betti: Mike, Mike!
迈克:(喊叫)……伙计,棒极了.你们过得怎样?你们太早了……我还没定比萨呢.
Mike: (shouted)&amp;amp;  Man that was good. Guys how you doing? You're early and  I haven't got pizza yet.
贝迪:我来,我表哥格斯在比萨店工作.我能打个折.
Betti: Let me do it. My cousin Gus works for Paradise pizza. I can get us a discount.
迈克:好的.
Mike: All right.
鲍纳:那么,迈可,我们怎么过?
Boner: So, Mike, what's the action?
迈克:随便,随便,我们吃着比萨看会电视.
Mike: Not much, not much. Eat a little pizza and watch a little TV.
鲍纳:看电视?迈克,家里没其他人,这是个生活中难得的的机会,你就只想看电视?
Boner: TV? Mike, your folks aren't home, This is a chance of life time and you wanna watch TV?
迈克:电视已经开始了.
Mike: It's already started.
鲍纳:迈克,你怎么能对电视这么……呃……哦,几时安的有线电视?
Boner: Mike, what could be so important&amp;amp;.. Wah&amp;amp; so, when did you get cable?
贝迪:好极了.格斯表哥说比萨不要钱.
Betti: This is great. Gus is going to let us have the pizzas for nothing.
迈克:太好了!
Mike: All right!
贝迪:但是他下班要带几个朋友一块来.
Betti: If he and a couple of friends can stop by after work?
迈克:你知道有几个人?因为我想人不能太多……
Mike: You know how many? Because I don't think we should have more.
贝迪:他说有女的……
Betti: Imagine women..
迈克:哦,好吧.
Mike: All right.
开萝尔:剩下的旅途也这么充满乐趣吗?
Carol: Is the rest of the trip going to be this much fun?
麦琪:开萝尔,你为什么不和本一起去外公房里看电视呢?
Maggie: Carol, why don't you and Ben go watching TV in grandpa's den?
本:太棒了!
Ben: Great!
开萝尔:当然了,对你来说当然好了;有我陪着消磨时间.
Carol: Sure, It's great for you; you get to spend time with me.
杰森:本,你别动你外公的任何警察装备.
Jason: Ben, don't you go touching any of your grandpa's police staff.
本:你知道我的.
Ben: You know me.
麦琪:杰森,我们要帮帮他们.
Maggie: Jason, we got to help them.
杰森:我不知道你的父亲是否想要我们帮忙.再说我懂些什么?我只不过是个得到证书的江湖医生.
Jason: I'm not so sure your dad wants our help. Then again what do I know? I'm just a licensed quack.
麦琪:哦,杰森.
Maggie: Oh, Jason.
外公:不许动小子!
Grandpa: Freeze slime bag!
麦琪:爸爸!
Maggie: Daddy!
外婆:埃德,你差点打到杰森!
Grandma: Ed, you almost shot Jason!
外公:哦,他们不应该在这儿!呃……谁也不应该在这儿.
Grandpa: Well, they are not supposed to be here! Eh.., no one's supposed to be here.
麦琪:哦,妈妈,你还好吧?见到你真高兴!
Maggie: Oh, mom, how are you? It's so good to see you!
妈妈:我很好,哦……你们是不是说过要来的,但我忘了?
Mom: I'm fine, Oh&amp;amp;Did you say you were coming and I forgot?
麦琪:没有,妈妈.
Maggie: No, mom.
杰森:埃德,见到你我总是觉得很高兴.
Jason: Ed, it's always a pleasure to see you.
麦琪:爸爸,爸爸,爸爸!
Maggie: Daddy, daddy, daddy!
外公:小南瓜!
Grandpa: Pumpkin!
麦琪:你要卖房子这到底是怎么回事呢?
Maggie:  So what's this about selling the house?
外公:哦,这个,我们打算退休以后就卖.然后搬到一个小地方居住这样可以节省一些.
Grandpa: oh, well, we thought we'd do this retirement thing right.  Move into a smaller place with less up keep.
外婆:住公寓.
Grandma: A condo.
开萝尔:外公,外婆!
Carol: Grandma, grandpa!
外婆:开萝尔,宝贝
Grandma: Carol, honey!
外公:看她长得这么大了!哈哈.
Grandpa: Look how she's grown! Hehe
外婆:迈克呢?
Grandma: Where's Mikey?
麦琪:哦,迈克他来不了,而且……
Maggie: Oh, Mike couldn't come, and&amp;amp;
本:外公!
Ben: Grandpa!
外公:那是本吗?
Grandpa: Is that Benni?
麦琪:对!
Maggie: Yeah!
外公:好啦!举起双手然后进来.
Grandpa: All right! Come out with your hands up!
本:我没法举,开萝尔把我铐在椅子上了.
Ben: I can't. Carol handcuffed me to the chair!
外公:哈!守着门;我来收拾他.
Grandpa: ha! Watch the door; I'm gonna rough him up.
本:呵呵,哦,住手我会逮住你的.
Ben: Hehe, oh, stop it I'll get you
麦琪:哦,我们歇会吧,该去弄晚饭了.来吧,本,.让你爸爸和外公说会话.
Maggie: Oh, we're going to stop and fix a little dinner, come on, Ben. Let your dad and granddad talk.
外公:哦,我想没那个必要.
Grandpa: Oh, I don't think that'll be necessary.
杰森:不,他可以在这里玩.
Jason: No, he can play here.
麦琪:来吧,本,你帮着削土豆皮.
Maggie: Come on, Ben, you can peel potatoes with the other persons.
本:哦.
Ben: Wow
麦琪:爸爸,如果你和妈妈有经济问题的话,我们会……
Maggie: Daddy, if you and mom are having financial problems we would be
外公:不,我们有.很好,一切都很顺利.
Grandpa: No, they're swell. It's well, fine, even good.
麦琪:爸爸,不管你需要多少钱,我和杰森都很高兴…
Maggie: Dad, any money you need, Jason and I would be more than happy
外公:麦琪,你忘记了吗我的小女儿,我供你住供你吃足足有18年,直到他来了把你带走.
Grandpa: Maggie, just in case you can't remember little girl, I kept a roof over your head and food on the table for over 18 years, till he came along anyway.
麦琪:爸爸!
Maggie: Daddy!
外公:不要说了.我现在不靠你们的施舍还能够养活你妈妈和我自己.
Grandpa: Damn it I can still take care of your mom and myself without your charity.
杰森:爸爸,爸爸,你没理由拒绝我们的帮助,就因为你对我有些看法.
Jason: Dad, dad, please! It's no reason for you to turn down this offer just because how you feel about me.
麦琪:杰森,你不要提……
Maggie: Jason, let's not mention&amp;amp;
杰森:不,不.你爸爸应该克服对我的看法,它应该保住这房子.为什么因为这愚蠢的自尊心而伤老伴,女儿和你自己的心?
Jason: No, no. Your dad should overcome his feelings about me and save this house. Why hurt your wife, your daughter and yourself all in the name of some foolish pride.
外公:愚蠢!别用江湖医生那套话来跟我说!告诉你除非我死了,否则我不会收你一个子儿!
Grandpa: Foolish! Don't use your shrink talk on me! The day I accept one dime of your money  will be the day they bury me.
杰森:进展很顺利,是吗?
Jason: I think that went well, don't you?
男孩:是的,杰瑞,听着,告诉布鲁斯,罗宾汉55号现在正在开派对.
Boy: Yeah, Jerry, listen. Call Bruce Vineger, tell him the party's at central 15, Robinhood lane.
迈克:啊,对不起,你叫懒虫是吗?我认为不应该再请更多的人了.
Mike: Ah, excuse me. Slug is it? I don't think we should invite any more people.
男孩:跟你有什么关系?你没听见吗?那个住在这儿的家伙,他父母去外地了.
Boy: What's up to you? Didn't you hear? The bozo who lives heres, parents are out of town.
迈克:家伙?嘿,听着.
Mike: Bozo? Hey, listen.
女孩:嗨,迈克.记得我吗?琳达……我们一起练过空手道.
Girl: Hi, Mike. Remember me? Linda mcmannis, We were in Karate class together.
迈克:我知道,我记得你,你那双杀人手够厉害……啊,我是说,我是说……
Mike: Yeah, yeah, of course I remember you. You have got killer hands. Ah, I mean, I mean&amp;amp;
女孩:我知道你的意思.
Girl: I know what you mean.
贝迪:迈克,到这里来.
Betti: Mike, come here.
迈克:请允许我失陪一秒.
Mike: could you excuse me just a second?
女孩:好的.就一秒.
Girl: OK. just for a second.
贝迪:迈克,有两个家伙在后院呕吐,还有一个在楼上刮胡子呢.
Betti: Michel, there are two guys out back throwing up and one upstairs is shaving.This has
这可是我参加过的最酷的宴会了.
got to be the coolest party I have ever been to.
迈克:刮胡子?
Mike: Shaving?
贝迪:迈克,我需要几块钱,你妈妈的车子没油了.
Betti: Mike, I need a couple of bucks, your mom's car ran out of gas.
迈克:嘿,你不能用我妈妈的车.
Mike: hey, you can't take my mom's car.
贝迪:不是我,是弗兰克.
Betti: I didn't, Frank did.
迈克:弗兰克是谁?
Mike: Who's Frank?
贝迪:我还以为你认识他.
Betti: I thought you knew him.
迈克:不认识.
Mike: No.
贝迪:听着.格斯送比萨的车子发动不起来了,,所以他打电话给弗兰克叫他开车去拿我们的比萨,既然是免费的就让我们帮忙送几批货.
Betti: All right. Gus's pizza- mobile wouldn't start, so he calls Frank and say's we're gonna have to pick up our own pizzas and since they are free could we make a couple of deliveries.
迈克:用我妈妈的车?
Mike: In my mom's car?
贝迪:那你叫弗兰克怎么做?
Betti: What was Frank supposed to do?
迈克:那么弗兰克应该怎么做?
Mike: What was Frank supposed to do?
贝迪:所有的事都在掌控之中.你就给点汽油钱吧.
Betti: Everything is under control. Now just give me a little gas money.
麦琪:妈妈,你就叫爸爸拿这笔钱吧.这也是你的家.
Maggie: Mom, make dad take the money. It's your home too.
外婆:哦,这个家是你爸爸是主人,在婚礼那天我保证过,要爱他,敬他,服从他.
Grandma: Well, your father's the boss, and on our wedding day I promised to love, honour and obey.
麦琪:哦,妈妈,妈妈.每个现代女性都知道服从只是口头上说说的.
Maggie: Oh, mom, mom. Every modern woman knows obey is just a figure of speech.
外婆:也许那就是为什么现在每个现代女性似乎都想离婚的原因.
Grandma: Maybe that's why every modern womon seems to get divorced.
杰森:凯特,孩子们围在钢琴边等着你唱首歌呢.
Jason: Kate either the kids are glued to the piano or they're waiting for one of your songs.
外婆:哦,好的,我刚刚弄到一首音乐"像个处女".
Grandma: Oh, good. I just got the sheet music to like a virgin
杰森:事实上他们不是粘在那儿,他们全被铐起来了.
Jason: Actually they are not glued, they are handcuffed.
麦琪:哦,杰森,我跟妈妈说不通.得靠我们两个了,你说我们该怎么做?
Maggie: Oh, Jason, I got no where with my mother, It's up to us, what are we gonna do?
杰森:我们该怎么做?我完全没有一点主意.
Jason: What are we gonna do? I don't have the slightest idea.
麦琪:我们不能让他们把房子卖掉.杰森,他们所需要的就是六千美元.
Maggie: We can't let them lose their home. Jason, all they need is six thousand dollars.
杰森:如果我说错了你可以纠正我,但我们不是愿意给你父亲钱吗?
Jason: Correct me if I'm wrong but didn't we just offer your father money?
麦琪:你就因为他说了他宁愿去死也不要你给他的钱你就放弃了吗?
Maggie: and you're giving up just because he said he's rather be dead?
杰森:原谅我,那我该怎么办?
Jason: Forgive me, what was I thinking?
麦琪:好吧,你的计划是什么?
Maggie: OK, so what's your plan?
杰森:我没有什么计划.
Jason: I don't have a plan.
麦琪:你认为没有任何计划就行动这样明智吗?
Maggie: Do you think it's wise to proceed without a plan?
女孩A:这张唱片我们刚听过.
Girl A: We've just heard this record.
女孩B:没关系.乐队应该马上就要过来了.
Girl B: That's OK, the band should be here any minute.
迈克:乐队?
Mike: Band?
迈克:鲍纳,这场派对已经完全失控了.
Mike: Boner, this party is completely out of control.
鲍纳:我知道,老兄,祝贺你!
Boner: I know man, congratulations!
迈克:我得想个办法停止这些,不然的话别人会说我太无能了.
Mike: I gotta do something to stop it without all these people thinking I'm a wimp
鲍纳:放松点,迈克,今晚是你创造派对历史记录的时机.
Boner: Relax, Mike. It's time to make party history.
迈克:对不起.这个给我好吗?
Mike: Excuse me. Mind if I cut in?
迈克:我已经风流过15年了.你好,警察局吗?对,我是甘地先生.是的,鲍勃·甘地.
Mike: At least I was cool for 15 years. Hello, police? Yeah, this is Mr. Ghandi. Yes, Bob Ghandi.
是,我住在罗宾汉巷,而且我爱好和平.这里非常安静的街道,可有个派对闹得非常厉害,就在15号.对,
Yes, I'm a very peace loving man, and I'm living on Robinhood lane. It is a normally a very peaceful street, but tonight there is a very very big loud party in No.15. Yes, I believe it's the
那是希弗家,是难以相信,因为他们一向是爱好安静的.是的,
Seavor home. This is very hard to believe since they are such a loving, peaceful family, yes.
请你们务必好好对待希弗家一个叫迈克的小伙子,他可是个非常非常精神的孩子,我肯定这不是他的过失.
And please be going easy on the Seavor boy called Mike, he's a very very spiritual boy and none of this could possibly be his fault.
麦琪:还是忙音,我在想迈克会是在跟谁说电话呢?
Maggie: Still busy, I wonder who Mike could be talking to?
开萝尔:妈妈,过来到你了.
Carol: Mom, come and take your turn.
本:耶.
Ben: Yeah.
外婆:我做得对吗?
Grandma: Am I doing this right?
杰森:他在自己的房间里?
Jason: Is he in his den?
麦琪:对.
Maggie: Yeah.
杰森:好吧,麦琪.你让我拿出一个计划来的.
Jason: OK, Maggie. You are the one who wanted me to come up with a plan.
麦琪:你想怎么去做?
Maggie: What are you going to do?
杰森:我不知道.
Jason: I have no idea.
杰森:埃德?
Jason: Ed?
外公:你来提供另一个慈悲,对吗?
Grandpa: Come to make another generous offer, did you?
杰森:你准备好了来个断然拒绝?
Jason: Ready for another gracious turn down?
杰森:我并不是想提什么建议埃德,除了道歉.给.
Jason: Now I didn't come to offer you anything Ed, except an apology. Here.
外公:爱尔兰威士忌?
Grandpa: Irish Whisky?
杰森:我想,我承认内心深处确实想通过给你钱而让你难堪.对不起.
Jason: Well, you know, I thought that maybe deep down I really did want to embarrass you a little by offering you that money I admit that, I'm sorry.
外公:坐下.拿两个玻璃杯.
Grandpa: Sit down. Grab a couple of glasses.
杰森:好的.来盘跳棋怎么样?
Jason: OK. Game a checkers?
外公:好的.
Grandpa: Sure.
杰森:在这些瓶子里加姜汁酒怎么弄?
Jason: How we gonna get any ginger ale in those glasses?
外公:姜汁酒?这是威士忌.
Grandpa: Ginger ale? That's Irish man.
杰森:可你不能直接就喝这酒.
Jason: You can't drink that straight.
外公:小看我!
Grandpa: Blasphemy!
杰森:哦,说大话.
Jason: Oh, big talk.
外公:哦,看着吧
Grandpa: Oh, just watch.
杰森:一小口不算大人物.你能把它全喝干吗?
Jason: A one sip big deal. Bet you can't drain that?
外公:你就看着吧.
Grandpa: Keep watching.
杰森:赌一百美元.
Jason: One hundred dollars.
外公:当然可以.
Grandpa: You're on.
外公:我赢了一百美元.
Grandpa: One hundred dollars!
杰森:哦,这算什么?赌注加倍我也行.
Jason: Well, can't be that tough? Double or nothing says that I can do it.
外公:你?哈哈,来吧.
Grandpa: You? Hehe. You are on.
外公:哈哈,我又赢了.
Grandpa: Hah, I won again.
杰森:你得给我个机会让我和你打个平局.
Jason: You have to give me a chance to get even.
麦琪:本,开萝尔.
Maggie: Ben and Carol.
本和开萝尔一起:上床了!
Ben and Carol together: Go to bed!
迈克:哦,警察怎么还不来?警察在哪呢?
Mike: Oh, where are the cops? Where are the cops?
有人:我们需要更多的空间来跳舞.
Someone: We need more room to dance.
有人:我们把家具都放到厨房去
Someone: Let's put all the furniture into the kitchen.
贝迪:啊,迈克,跟你妈妈说应该把刹车检查一下了.哦,弗兰克睡在后座呢.唱片上的东西,是他吐的,不是我.
Betti: Ah, Mike, tell your mother, she should have her breaks checked. Oh, Frank is asleep in the backseat. And for the record, he puked, not me.
迈克:好吧,够了.警察来不来舞会都得结束.就像我的生命也该彻底结束了.
Mike: All right, that's it. Cops or no Cops this party is over. Just like my life.
迈克:嗨,我是迈克.我是这场派对的发起人.我有几句话要说.
Mike: hi, I'm Mike. I'm the bozo giving this party. I've got something to say.
鲍纳:大事件.
Boner: Big deaI.
迈克:嘿.
Mike: Hey!
鲍纳:迈克,你这可不酷了.
Boner: Mike, you know this is not cool.
迈克:我不管.我要你们大家,尤其是你,懒虫,给我……
Mike: I don't care. I want all you people, especially you slug, just...
警察:开门!警察!
Police: open up! Police!
迈克:噢,好的,好的,天啊谁叫来了警察.舞会才刚进行呢.
Mike: Oh, nice, nice, now who called the police. Come on, this party was just starting to cool.
杰森:噢,不行了,够了.我完了.这是你最后一次赢我了,埃德.
Jason: Oh, no, that's it. I'm gone. You beat me for the last time, Ed.
外公:哈哈,根据我的记录,我一共赢了你了7次.而且加倍,从一百开始.
Grandpa: Haha, by my records, you lost seven times. Yes, that's double or nothing, starting at a hundred.
杰森:对的.
Jason: Right.
外公:那么你欠我2倍,4倍,16倍,32倍,64倍.6400美元!
Grandpa: So you owe me one goes to two, that's four, sixteen thirty two, sixty four hundred dollars. Sixty four hundred dollars!
杰森:什么?
Jason: What?
外公:我算的是这个数.我没作假.
Grandpa: That's what it comes to. I don't get it, either.
杰森:哦,对,你没有.不,不,干得不错,我算服了你了.
Jason: Oh, sure, you don't. No, no, nice job, you got me.
外公:我究竟怎么回事?我才喝了三杯,可是你连一杯也没喝完.
Grandpa: How did I do that? I only had three shots and you never got all the way through one of yours.
杰森:埃德大叔最终压倒了虚有外表的心理医生.
Jason: So Big Ed finally shows the overpaid psychiatrist who's smarter. I don't like to be taken,
我可不想被骗,埃德.
Ed.
外公:难道我欺骗你了?我光明正大赢你的.
Grandpa: I didn't take you. I won that fair and square.
杰森:哦,我可不给!
Jason: Well, I am not paying.
外公:你敢不给?我要我的钱 .
Grandpa: The hell you are not? I want my money.
麦琪:怎么了?
Maggie: Well?
外公:杰森,你把我的6400美元给我才能离开这个房子.
Grandpa: Jason, you are not leaving this house until I get my six thousand four hundred dollars.
外婆:埃德,我们保住了我们的房子,你也保住了你的自尊.
Grandma: Eddy, we get to keep our house, and you get to keep your pride.
外公:嗨,我告诉过你我这老头靠得住,是吗?
Grandpa: Hey, I told you I take care of you, didn't I ?
麦琪:谢谢,亲爱的.
Maggie: Thank you, honey.
杰森:嘿,我不光丢了6千美元,而且我的肚子还疼得难受.
Jason: hi, I just lost six grand and I may lose my lunch.
麦琪:我知道你还得照顾我.
Maggie: I knew you'd take care of me.
迈克:谢谢你们的帮助,警官,这些我能解决.
Mike: Thanks for your help officer; I can handle it from here.
警察:你真是非常非常客气,甘地先生,哈哈哈哈……
Police: You are very very welcome, Mr. Gandhi Hahaha.
迈克:啊……
Mike: Ah
迈克:欢迎爸爸妈妈回来.
Mike: Welcome home mom and dad.
本:闪开,别挡道.
Ben: Out of my way! Nature calls.
杰森:迈克,你的周末过的怎么样?
Jason: Mike, how was your weekend?
迈克:哦,没劲的那种.你们和外婆外公一起过的周末还好吗?
Mike: Oh, kind of boring. How was your weekend with grandma and grandpa?
杰森:哦,还好,还好.
Jason: Oh, fine, fine.
麦琪:事实上你爸爸这个周末成了英雄,他拯救了一栋房子.
Maggie: Actually your father was a hero this weekend, he saved the house.
迈克:哦,真的吗?真是太巧了!
Mike: Oh, really? What a coincidence!
杰森:什么太巧了?
Jason: What?
迈克:啊,我是说你们在那儿,我在这儿,这是个奇妙的世界.
Mike: Ah, It's nice to know you guys were up there, and I was down here, hey, it's a wonderful world.
开萝尔:我以为你的施肥工作应该在昨天就结束了.
迈克:哪来的狗?
Carol: I thought your manure spreading job was over yesterday.
00:23:02,300
Mike: What dog?